再来点柠檬水吗  先生
More lemonade, sir?
事先声明  这其实是一壶
Full disclosure, it's a pitcher of water
我们去不掉柠檬味的水
we can't get the lemon taste out of.
先生
Sir?
麦克斯  这男的如果不是装死
Max, either this guy's pretending to be dead
来骗霸王餐
to get out of paying the check
就是奥列格的辣椒又害死人了
or Oleg's chili has killed again.
这是我的厄尔小镜
This is my Earl mirror.
是我在他小睡时专门用来探鼻息的神器
I use it during naps to make sure he's still breathing.
而八成时候他都还有呼吸
And 80% of the time he is.
阿憨  第三桌有个死人
Han, there's a dead body at table three,
这是除了第二桌之外  最悲哀的死处了
the saddest place to die other than table two.
奥列格快出来
Oleg, get out here!
有人比麦克斯的内心还死翘翘
Someone's deader than Max's emotions.
我真该把那批辣椒给扔了
I really should throw away that chili.
把他放到街上  再放个捐款筒
Let's prop him up outside with a Salvation Army bucket.
他这尸体能讨到多少善款  我们明早分了
Whatever he collects, we split in the morning.
我就不参加了
Uh, count me out.
如果条子抓到我们五个人与这个尸体
If they catch the five of us with a dead body,
想都不用想  肯定是我这黑人扛罪
you know they're gonna blame the black guy.
一人抓一肢把他抬起来
Okay, everyone grab a limb and lift.
餐点味道还满意吗
How's everything tasting?
麦克斯  你一定不敢信
Max, you're not gonna believe it.
鲍比在我们家洗澡呢
Bobby's in the shower!
他就是这么喜欢我  连我们家浴室都敢用
That's how much he likes me, he's using our shower.
他令我太开心了
He makes me so happy.
我都"听"到了
Yeah, I heard.
那叫声听起来像是有人想在我们家
It sounded like someone was trying to connect
用拨号上网一样
with a dial-up modem out here.
对不起啦
Sorry.
我连"上"网时就是这声响
That's just what I sound like when I go online.
但说真的  他让我每分每秒都如此快乐
But really, he makes me feel like that all the time.
他好完美  我跟他太完美
He's perfect. We're perfect.
卡洛琳  你别一下子就忘乎所以
Caroline, you shouldn't get too carried away.
世上没有什么完美的事
Nothing is perfect.
除了我帮纽约洋基队投球的那场完全比赛
Except that game I pitched for the Yankees.
其实真的是完美无缺
Actually, it is perfect.
我跟他是天生一对
We're amazing together,
而且我也不想听毒鸡汤女王的评论
and I really don't want to hear from Negative Nancy.
谁...  谁是毒鸡汤女王啊
What the... who's Negative Nancy?
谁不知道老娘的诨号是"毒奶波霸"
Everyone knows I go by "Negative Juggs McGee."
我只是想说你还没真正了解他
I'm just saying you don't know him that well yet.
我知道你为什么这么说  跟我与鲍比无关
I know what this is about, and it's not me and Bobby.
你是担心我哪天受伤
You're worried I'm gonna get hurt
因为有你跟兰迪的前车之鉴
because of what happened between you and Randy.
跟那个才没关系
It's not about that.
我只是特别了解男人
I just know guys,
而你上一次谈恋爱的时候
and you haven't been in a relationship
大本还是最棒的那个阿弗莱克呢
since Ben was the best Affleck.
两位
Hey there.
真是绝了  我洗完澡后
It's amazing, I'm somehow less clean now
莫名其妙比洗之前更脏了
than when I went in.
宝贝  我得先走了
I gotta get going, babe.
到时候跟你在甜品酒吧见
I'll meet you at the dessert bar.
我们要跟他妈妈与姐姐共进午餐
We're having lunch with his mom and his sister.
我也差不多算是家庭的一员了
I'm almost part of the family now.
如果你真的是我家的人
Well, if you were part of the family
那你会对无糖百事可乐上瘾
you'd be addicted to Diet Pepsi
而且会在黑色星期五特卖跟人打起来
and get into mall fights on Black Friday.
那我们可能是亲戚啊
Then I might be a cousin.
这样吧  我送你出去
Oh, you know what? I'll walk you out.
要是流浪汉拉里想抓你
If Homeless Larry tries to grab you,
-我可以把他挡开  -好啊
- I can fend him off. - Yeah.
小心点  他现在还有兵器烤肉夹了
Oh, careful, he's got barbecue tongs now.
看看这对小情侣
Look at those two.
大庭广众秀恩爱让我想"自己身寸...
That PDA is making me want to M-A-S-T-U...
我想让你别说
Ah, I would stop you,
但我好奇你"身寸"后面接什么
but I doubt you know what comes after U.
身寸"我"后面
Usually me.
你们俩有何企图
What do you guys want?
我们想找点新娱乐
Well, we're looking for some entertainment.
我跟奥列格最近狂看了各种节目
Oleg and I have binge-watched everything.
我们连超难看的《小镇滋味》都看了
You know, we even watched the Santa Clarita Diet.
那可真是这辈子都不想再尝的"滋味"啊
Now that's one diet I'm not gonna stick to.
鲍比好像把手机忘在这里了
Oh, Bobby must have left his phone here.
-靠  -怎么了
- Oh, crap. - What's wrong?
是鲍比的前女友杰西卡的短信
It's a text from Bobby's ex, Jessica.
写着"打给我  是宝宝的事"
It says, "Call me about baby."
鲍比跟杰西卡有宝宝了吗
Do Bobby and Jessica have a baby?
还是他们要生一个
Are they going to have one?
还有为什么鲍比会用玫瑰金的苹果手机啊
And why does Bobby have a rose gold iPhone?
说不定是他做年度乳房摄影检查时送的
Maybe he got it with his yearly mammogram.
我就知道这段感情好得蹊跷
I knew this relationship was too good to be true.
我果然不是毒鸡汤女王
Looks like I'm not Negative Nancy,
而是醒醒吧一姐
more like Reality Check Rita.
那我以前干嘛叫你麦克斯啊
Then why the hell have I been calling you Max?
先提醒一下
Oh, just a heads-up,
鲍比的家人正在来的路上
Bobby's family is on its way over,
你想做的任何限制级布偶演出
so any X-rated puppeteering you have to do,
请在现在就表演完
now is the time.
说到鲍比与他认识的人
Speaking of Bobby and people he knows,
他跟那个什么杰西卡还有联络吗
uh, does he still talk to what's-her-name, Jessica?
当然没有
Pfft, no.
早已是过去式  就如同我的刘海
She is long gone, like my bangs
与这国家的民主一样
or democracy.
鲍比从来不会提起她
Bobby never brings her up.
我们通常都是聊我们的共同爱好
We just talk about our common interests,
比如我们有多喜欢我的秀发
like how much we like my hair
以及我有多漂亮
or how pretty I am.
再绕回刚才说到的其他人
Yeah, but circling back to other people,
真的很难跟你聊除你以外的事物
which is very hard with you,
杰西卡  他们还有通话  短信
Jessica, do they talk? Text?
或共同抚养权吗
Share custody?
麦克斯  你为什么一直要问她
Max, why are you asking about her?
杰西卡是他的前女友
Jessica is his ex-girlfriend.
鲍比只说过她是一名婚礼规划师
All Bobby's ever said about her is that she's a wedding planner
他们早就没联络了
and she's out of his life.
我知道这对你来说很难相信
I know that's hard for you to believe,
就像当年的月球登陆一样
like the moon landing.
又没人看见太空人的脸
You never see their faces.
他们也没有带回来乳酪  信不信由你
They brought back no cheese. Just saying.
-好了  你别在扯这事  -好啦
- Now, please, just drop it. - Fine-ah!
好啦
Fine-ah.
丹妮斯你来啦
Oh, hi, Denise.
你妈妈跟鲍比呢
Where's your mom and Bobby?
我们不搭同一班地铁
Oh, we don't ride the subway together
以防发生意外时全家团灭
in case there's a crash.
家里总得有人活着迎战黑色星期五特卖
Somebody's gotta be around for Black Friday.
现在鲍比的姐姐来了
Well, now that Bobby's sister is here,
我就不给你们的完美早午餐添乱了
I don't wanna mess up your perfect brunch.
我要过去餐厅了  那里唯一完美的事物
I'm going to the diner, where the only perfect thing
就是猫头鹰与老鼠的黄金比例
is the owl-to-rat ratio.
所以这家店是你的啊
So you own this place?
我也好希望能当自己的老板
Man, I'd love to be my own boss.
我老板把我当垃圾一样对待
Mine treats me like garbage.
如果我想在休息时间跟快递员"搞一发"
If I want to get freaky with the UPS guy on my break,
那也是我的私人时间
that's my time.
所以你除了搞快递员还搞些什么
So what is it you do, besides the UPS guy?
我在"邮寄与其他事务"公司的柜台工作
I work the counter at the Mail Boxes and Other Things.
很像"邮寄与其他"公司  但我们有"其他事务"
It's like Mail Boxes Etc, but we have other things.
我知道听起来很酷炫
I know it sounds cool,
但我老板总是找我麻烦
but my boss is always on me.
或许你该跟你老板谈谈
Well, maybe you should talk to your boss.
把你的心情告诉他  维护自己的权利
You know, tell him how you feel, stand up for yourself.
我不太擅长跟人正面对峙
I'm not great with confrontation,
部分原因是因为我不知"深浅"
partially because I had bad depth perception.
比如我现在就搞不清你跟我的距离
Like, I have no idea how far away you are right now.
我就在这
I'm right here.
在"二垒"上
On second base.
我觉得你人很好
Well, I think you're great,
而且行为完全不会不合适
and not inappropriate at all.
如果你的老板看不出这点  或许你该辞职
And if your boss can't see that, well, maybe you should quit.
那个看起来像林肯总统的男人
So the gentleman who looked like Abraham Lincoln,
是留胡子的非主流  还是正统犹太人
was that a hipster or an Orthodox Jew?
无论是哪种  我不懂你为啥塞给人家一块钱
Either way, I don't understand why you gave him a dollar.
妈  我辞职
Mom, I quit!
等等  你妈就是你老板吗
Wait, your mom is your boss?
是因为快递员吗
Is it the UPS man?
他可是你教父啊  太有违伦理了
He's your godfather. It's untoward.
辞职想法哪来的
Where's this coming from?
我最新的挚友
From my new best friend
以及商界女性的导师
and women-in-business mentor,
卡洛琳
Caroline.
你让我女儿从我这里辞职吗
You told my daughter to quit working for me?
我相信她是在说另一个卡洛琳
I'm sure she meant a different Caroline.
我不知道啊
I don't know.
她摸完我胸之后  我意识就模糊了
Everything got blurry after she touched my boobs.
阿憨  我要对你说一句
Han, I'm about to say what you said to me
你让我带你去看限制级电影时说的话了
when you were trying to get into an R-rated movie.
我需要你的帮忙
I need your help.
我跟你说过三次了  我钻不进排水管
I told you three times, I don't fit up drain pipes.
听我说  我在鲍比的手机上
Listen, I just saw this text on Bobby's phone
看到他前女友杰西卡给他的短信
from his ex-girlfriend, Jessica.
我觉得他们私底下有个宝宝
I think they might have a secret baby together.
这事绝对会让卡洛琳崩溃
Wow, that would really devastate Caroline.
但更重要的是
More importantly,
我跟鲍比是玫瑰金兄弟啊
Bobby and I are rose gold buddies.
我想在说出任何让卡洛琳惊慌失措的话前
I just have to make sure before I say anything
先去确认过
to panic Caroline.
我想先去明察暗访一下
I need to do some detective work,
你跟我一起去
so you and I are gonna go down
杰西卡的婚礼规划公司
to Jessica's wedding planning business
然后假装是一对情侣
and pretend we're a couple.
显然  我来当新郎
Obviously I'll be the groom.
麦克斯  这事虽然你可能听了会惊讶
Max, this might come as a surprise to you,
但我很忙好吗
but I'm a very busy man.
我没时间陪你去幼稚胡闹
I don't have time for your sophomoric high jinks.
大家也这么说亚当·桑德勒的喜剧电影
Uh, that's what they said to Adam Sandler,
结果只让他更富上加富了
and it only made him richer.
作为你的陪伴首选  我深感荣幸
I'm flattered I was your first choice.
兄弟  我早你好几轮就被邀请了
Man, she asked me five people ago.
她好像问到最后就剩你跟扫帚
I think she was down to you or a broom,
而扫帚又在忙
and the broom was busy.
如果我真陪你去  那我们得拿出最佳的演技
If I'm doing this, we have to use our best acting skills,
毕竟谁会相信你能钓到我这金龟婿
'cause who's gonna believe you landed me?
要是"扫帚"先生4点没普拉提课就好了
Ugh, really wish Steve the Broom didn't have Pilates at 4:00.
真的很对不起  菲拉罗太太
I'm so sorry, Mrs. Ferraro.
我真的不知道你就是那个
I had no idea you were the awful boss
让她生活苦不堪言的恶魔老板
that was making her life miserable.
鲍比  你为何没告诉我
Bobby, why didn't you tell me
你妈妈有一家"邮寄与其他事务"啊
your mom owns a Mail Boxes and Other Things?
我怕你因为我家无限量的气泡膜而爱我
I didn't want you to date me for the unlimited bubble wrap.
丹妮斯无法适应外面世界
Denise can't cope out in the world.
你明知道她摸过
You know how many times she's touched
我们邻居的通电篱笆多少回了
our neighbor's electric fence.
讲道理  他们装电篱笆
To be fair, they installed it
也是为了防止她再掉进他们泳池
to keep her from falling in their pool.
事是你惹的  你得负责摆平
Well, you did this. You take care of it.
她现在是你的责任了
She's your responsibility now.
鲍比  帮我外带一点甜品回家
Bobby, bring home some deserts for me.
从甜甜圈连锁店带
From Dunkin'!
鲍比  真的很对不起
Bobby, I am so sorry.
我不想我们首次吵架是因为一些误会
I don't want our first fight to be over a misunderstanding.
我希望我们是因为某件大事而吵
I want it to be about something important,
比如你想留唇下一撮小胡子
like if you want a soul patch.
我们不是吵架
We're not fighting.
只是点小摩擦
This is a bump.
你反应过度了
I think you're overreacting.
那你干嘛吼我
Then why are you yelling?
我没吼你啊
I'm not yelling.
天啊  怎么吼成这样了
Man, what's with all the yelling?
奥列格  快来看好戏
Oh, Oleg, let's see where this goes.
已经比亚马逊拍的所有电视剧都好看了
It's already better than everything on Amazon.
要是能更《权力的游戏》风就好了
Just with it was a little bit more Game of Thrones-y.
鲍比露
Bobby.
卡洛琳  我们真不是吵架
Caroline, we're not fighting.
但拜托你以后别再介入
But please, don't get in the middle
我妈跟丹妮斯之间的事了
of my ma and Denise again.
我阿姨试过一次
My aunt tried once.
现在她超级害怕吊扇
Now she's really scared of ceiling fans.
我得走了  我还是找不到我的手机
I gotta go. I still can't find my phone.
奥列格  这是我们消遣的新节目
Oleg, this is our new show.
快把我包里的爆米花拿出来
Grab the popcorn from my purse.
你想吃咸的还是甜的
You want cheddar cheese or kettle corn?
你们知道我听得见你们说话  对吧
You know I can hear you, right?
这里肯定是杰西卡的办公室
Okay, this must be Jessica's office.
给  最好把这个戴上
Oh, here, better put this on for the bit.
这可是来自朝鲜
This was smuggled out of North Korea
是我曾祖父藏在屁股里偷带出来的
by my great-grandfather in his great backside.
经典的屁股形切割
Oh, the classic tush cut.
记住  我们是侦探
Now remember, we're detectives.
我是警花
We're like Cagney
而你是唯一能拖来跟我办案的家伙
and the only guy I could get to come with me.
你们好呀
Hi.
你们肯定是麦克斯和阿憨
You must be Max and Han.
我是杰西卡
I'm Jessica.
非常感谢你们能来店里
Thanks so much for coming in.
你们这对真是超级无敌可爱
Oh, you guys are so super cute.
我们的可爱度能直逼...宝宝吗
How does our cuteness compare to, say, a baby?
你们想得真远
Wow, you're thinking ahead.
还是你已经怀有小不点了
Or are you expecting a little one?
我已经有一个小不点了
Ha, I've already got a little one.
你呢
What about you?
取笑我的身型是我们专属的秀恩爱方式
Making fun of my size is kind of our thing.
比如还有  甜蜜地滚床单
Like, making sweet love.
所以我有"孩子"  你呢
So I'm with child. Are you?
老实说  我...
Actually, I'm...
关于婚礼
So for the wedding,
我想要自然主题
I was thinking of a nature theme.
在公园里举办  各种奇思妙想
Something in the park, whimsical of course,
比如彩灯和鲜花  以及一个大帐篷
with lanterns and flowers, a big tent.
你不是吧
Oh, oh, really?
小笑星你还想要大帐篷啊  别打断杰西卡
You want a big top, Pee-wee? Jessica was talking.
抱歉  亲爱的
Sorry, dear.
我老伴很讨厌我插嘴
The old ball and chain hates when I get a word in.
让我们长相厮守  永不插嘴
Sign me up for a lifetime.
抱歉  我刚没听清你说生小孩的事
Sorry, uh, I missed what you were saying about having a baby.
今天的主角可不是我
We're not here to talk about me.
是你们和你们的喜事[婚外情]
Let's talk about you and your affair.
放心  我绝对会有的
Oh, I'm definitely gonna have one.
多谢发短信给我  卡洛琳
Thanks for texting, Caroline.
自从你让我炒掉我妈后  我有点迷失方向
I've been a little lost since you made me quit my job with Ma.
大部分是因为我找不到来这儿的地铁
Mostly 'cause I couldn't find the L train.
但我看见一个男人杀一只鸡呢
But I saw a guy kill a chicken.
我是想着跟你聚一聚
I thought you and I could get together
一起想想你职业生涯的下一步该怎么走
and figure out your next career move,
其实不一定要往前走
which does not necessarily need to be forward.
不  我才不会回我妈的店里
No, I'm not going back to my ma's store
无论我有多怀念藏在箱子里
no matter how much I miss hiding in boxes
到处吓唬别人
and scaring people.
让我们发散思维  想想你该找什么工作
Well, let's brainstorm on your next career move.
我一直很想当模特
I've always wanted to be a model.
有人说我不穿裤子时美呆了
I've been told I look great with my pants down.
你的价值并不止于那身皮囊
You are more than just a body.
有时候我也不确定
Hmm, sometimes I'm not so sure.
不如我在这儿工作吧
Hey, what about working here?
能有多难  你都做得来
How hard can it be? You do it.
老实说  这份工作需要很多...
Actually, this job requires a lot...
你不用再说服我了  我就在这儿干了
You don't have to talk me into it. I'll do it.
把装有饮品的飞盘给我
Give me the Frisbee with the drinks on it.
好吧  你就帮忙到麦克斯回来就好
Okay, I guess you could help out until Max gets back.
又或者到有人受伤了  那个人很可能是我
Or until someone gets hurt, probably me.
傍晚时分  夕照城市
As magic hour descends over the city,
我和麦克斯将前往我们的蜜月套房
Max and I will retire to the honeymoon suite
而她会抱着我  跨过门槛
where she carries me over the threshold.
接下来会发生什么  想想都激动
Excited for what's to come.
反正来什么  我们俩都不会来[高潮]
Well, it's not gonna be either of us.
说回你吧  小杰
So, uh, back to you, Jess.
派对礼品可以是小指南针
Ooh, the party favors could be little compasses
这样能指引客人入席
that lead you to your table.
或引到一艘等着的逃生船
Or to a waiting escape boat.
你俩确定彼此适合结为夫妻吗
Are you sure you two are right for each other?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我爱死他了
I am obsessed with him.